ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 5981 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: LABOR UNITY
  - Convention, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Includes: Thursday AM Rodolfo Robles, California, Guatemala Coca Cola; Thursday lunch actor meeting; Wednesday: Chavez, Mazur, Roy Wade, Hightower; Tuesday PM resolutions - Kirland, "spontaneous" Demo.
  - Convention, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Includes: Wednesday, delegates speak; June 7, Winnipeg and Lichtenburg and other.
  - Convention. Issue., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Includes: speakers; audiences; Joyce Miller; Bruce Dunton; Bud Clark; Finley; Chet Makowski; Fox; Carmela Acampa, Local 51; J. Miller; retirees; Coretta King; Sheinkman; press; Lane Kirkland; Dominick Torre, Hudson Valley Jt. Bd.; Cisneros; Liz Smith; Ste
  - Convention (June 1981) Issue. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Includes: hanging the union sign; delegates with literature; delegates registering; Montreal delegation; Philip Hare speaks; art display; GTA Jt. Bd. delegates; new locals; Quebec delegates with headphones; meeting; Veronica Fox speaks; delegate reads; wo
  - Convention (June 1981) Issue. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Includes: labor history tour; delegate Paul Raunall, Local 2381; Educational Dept. display at Coho Hall; Canadian delegates; Antonio Zoccoli; new locals parade at Coho Hall; green ribbons; sergeant-at-arms at Coho Hall; delegates Diane Rowe & Roosevelt Br
  - Convention. Prints., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Includes: Local 1672, Cedartown, GA, member Joseph Chubb speaks; Demonstration at Coho Hall - newly chartered locals; Maxene Hammond speaks; Richard Kessler speaks; Stevens worker Bennett Taylor speaks; Vincent Tibolella studies financial statement; Local
  - Convention. Prints., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Includes: Black woman speaking; Clara Bozeman speaking; Black man speaking; various speeches; "Sheinkman for Secretary-Treasurer" signs; painting ACTWU sign.
  - Convention, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Includes: Acapulco restaurant; speeches; "Finley and Sheinkman" sign; cooking; New Hellas Cafe; close-up Black woman; speeches; newly chartered unions marching; Grady Cullum speaks; TV camera; ribbons.
  - Convention. Contact Sheets., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17-21)
    Includes: Contact sheets.
  - Convention, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21b)
  - Convention, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Includes: Brad Field, Local 1826, London, Ont.; J.P. Stevens marchers; Pierre LeBlanc of Local 1838, Cowansville, Quebec; Hispanic man speaking; Fletcher Bech, Local 710 Rock Hill, SC; Clarence Gittens of Local 116, Montreal; Swoboda with Chaikin
  - Convention, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22b)
  - Convention, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Convention, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 23b)
  - Convention, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Includes: group shots; buildings; audience; TWUA COPE director Bruce Dunton accepts COPE donations, Walt Rainey; Eula McGill speaking; delegate inquires about pamphlets at booth; ACWA and TWUA delegates ride escalators in hotel; convention delegate
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Includes: booths; audience; group shots; airport.
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Includes: airport group shots; hotel lobby group shots; audience shots.
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Includes: BC and Alberta, Canada table; audience; airport group shots; Independent Locals table; Buffalo Reg. Jt. Bd.; Chicago and Central States Jt. Bd.; Black man at booth.
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    -includes: Canadian delegates; registration sign; Cleveland Jt. Bd.; Quebec Joint Board; Baltimore Reg. Joint Board; group shot: Black delegates; Local 169; group shots.
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Includes: delegates; group shots; Southern Carolinas-Virginia Reg. Jt. Bd.; Southwest Regional Joint Board Arkansas District; Black women; man and small boy.
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Includes: delegates; Canadian delegates; hotel shots; Granite State Joint Board; Central Mass. Joint Board.
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Includes: Rhode Island Joint Board; group shots; Twin City Joint Board; Greater Northern Textile Jt. Bd.; booths.
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Includes: booths; audience; group shots; Puerto Rico Joint Board; Black women; Hudson Valley Area Joint Board; New England Tailors Joint Board; New England Reg. Joint Board; Montreal Joint Board.
  - Convention. Color., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Includes: Toronto Joint Board; Greater Toronto Joint Board; group shots; audience; Southwest Regional Joint Board Arkansas District; delegates.
  - Convention. Color Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 34 -- Includes: delegates; Montreal Joint Board; Stevens Workers; booths; group shots.
  - Convention. Color Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 35 -- Includes: delegates; tables; Greater Cornwall Joint Board; audience; Greater Toronto Joint Board.
  - Convention. Color Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 36 -- Includes: group shots; booths; Shirt & Leisurewear Joint Board; clapping; Greater New York Joint Board; Black women; Black man and woman; delegates.
  - Convention. Color Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 37 -- Includes: Chicago & Central States Joint Board; Pennsylvania Joint Board; group shots.
  - Convention. Color Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 38 -- Includes: Chicago & Central States Jt. Bd.; New England Reg. Joint Board; Toledo Joint Board; Cleveland Joint Board; Pennsylvania Joint Board; Philadelphia Joint Board; Central & So. Jersey Join
  - Convention. Color Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 39 -- Includes: Greater New York Joint Board; Local 340A; Northwest Reg. Joint Board; Portland Area Joint Board; booths; New York Joint Board; Hawaii Joint Board; Lehigh Valley Clothing Workers Joint Board.
  - Convention. Color Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 40 -- Includes: delegates; Black delegates.
  - Convention. Color Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 41 -- Includes: Pittsburgh Dist. Joint Board; Eastern PA Clothing Workers Jt. Bd.; Bi-County Joint Board; Minnesota Joint Board; Amal, Service and Allied Ind. Jt. Bd.; Southwest Reg. Joint Board; El Paso Join
  - Convention. Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 42 -- Includes: Man with Finley and Sheinkman sign; speech; Black woman giving speech; Farah Workers supporters; sign "Welcome Farah Workers"; man blowing up balloon; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America 2
  - Convention. Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 43 -- Includes: woman speaking; "Finley and Sheinkman" signs; man giving speech; speakers at podium; woman singing; luggage; Black woman speaking; "Murray for President" sign; banquet.
  - Convention. Photos., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 44 -- Includes: woman speaking; audience; man in sombrero; man in Finley hat; man speaking; couple dancing; Black couple dancing; protestors; United Farm Workers; Black man singing; balloon saying "The End".
  - Convention. Photos., 1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 45 -- Includes: man speaking; people dancing; man speaking; Dr. Lise Goulet and Dr. Paula Lebel give speech at joint board education conference, Montreal; meeting; FTQ protest; course on grievance procedure a
  - Convention (ACWA), 1976-1987 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 46 -- Includes: swearing in officers at 1976 convention; Black women, Jan. 1987 Atlanta; Minnie Hobbs speaks; Bertha Moore speaks; Finley and Farral shake hands; Farah workers on strike; group shots; speeches
  - Convention, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 47 -- Includes: May 1972 Convention shots; Farah workers on strike; dancing; cake; group shots; contact sheets; woman speaking; man giving speech; various men speaking; shots at podium; men at table with pape
  - Convention, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 48 -- Includes: Minnie Hobbs talking, Farah workers on strike; Asian woman speaking; speeches; Black man speaking; priest speaking; woman speaking; group shots; blonde speaking; 1972 "Finley & Sheinkman"
  - Convention (Misc.)., 1946-1975 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 49 -- Includes: woman speaking; audience; band, boy singing; confetti; partying; ACWA May 1946 convention; tables with delegates from all states, cities; man speaking at ACWU convention, 1962; checking union
  - Convention (Misc.)., 1972-1983 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 50 -- Includes: speeches; Black woman singing; Farah workers on strike; May 1972, 28th Convention shots; Hispanic man speaking; audience; 1983
  - Convention (Misc.)., 1990 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 52 -- Includes: guitar player; married couple, 1990 ACTWU Convention; Canadian volleyball team; Macy Adkins organizing; Mike Washington speaking; 1990 convention, wedding Moberley - Shebilske; DeJesus speech
  - Convention (Misc.) (Box 17, Folder 28)
    Includes: Evelyn Allen; speakers; booths; Alda Melo; Bertha Moore; Vicky Marashlian; CA delegates.
  - Convention (Misc.)., 1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 53 -- Includes: 1987 Convention, Southern Regional Jt. Bd.; Geraldine Ramsey; GCA demonstration; Pauline Yeung, Canada; Jenny Cortez; general celebration; Edie DeJesus; Strike, NJ; speeches; audience; man pla
  - Convention (Misc.). (Box 18, Folder 2)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 54 -- Includes: Election demonstration; Cesar Chavez speech; Civil Rights Committee; cartoon from Welcome Delegates Brochure; Retirees; Cuomo and Italians; Local 1629 Hermann Pierre; Mike Washington; Gloria B
  - Convention (Misc.) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 55 -- Includes: Black woman speaking; group shots of delegates; baby wearing ACTWU hat; Black man; Asian woman speaking; various speakers; Black man reading; picketers, mother and girl; delegate couple; speec
  - Convention (Misc.). (Box 18, Folder 4)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 56 -- Includes: Local 1733 and 1932 delegates; speeches; Black woman with microphone; audience; Frontier Hotel picketers.
  - Conyers, John Jr., 1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 57 -- Includes: close-up of Conyers; Conyers shaking hands; shots of Conyers with labor leaders; 1972 portrait; group shots.
  - CO-OP Residents Pre-Pay Taxes in NY. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 58 -- Includes: Mayor Koch, Elizabeth Parmalee, Carole Greitzer, Ruth Messinger, Harry S. Tishelman, Meriam Friedlander, David Smith, Harrison J. Goldin.
  - COPE - Fundraiser. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 59 -- Includes: contact sheet; girl modelling ACTWU jacket.
  - COPE, Milwaukee. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 60 -- Includes: contact sheets.
  - Coping with Inflation Story. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 61 -- Includes: Della Griffin, Local 151, Jack White, Inc., Milwaukee, operating machinery; Bill and Connie Bishop; Chet and Helen Kallek.
  - Coponi, Joseph. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 62 -- Includes: contact sheets; Coponi addresses picnic in Allentown, PA; Coponi retires; portrait; Coponi and Sol Stetin, Mount Airy Lodge; Coponi receives Spirit of Life Award, Duarte, California - Sheinkma
  - Cornell Labor College. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 63 -- Includes: contact sheets.
  - Cornwall School., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 64 -- Includes: May 8, 1978 Local 779 Andre Decoste and William Jodoin.
  - Cosmetica. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 65 -- Includes: Cosmetica lunch room; Louise Casais, Hattie House, Gloria Galaza, Mary Ann Falkowiski, Doris DeGroot and Lea Lepine.
  - Coss, Ken. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 66 -- includes: portrait.
  - Costanza, Anthony. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 67 -- includes: Costanza at desk.
  - Cotton Dust Conference. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 68 -- Includes: contact sheets; speeches at Holiday Inn; Cotton Dust Demonstration.
  - Cotton Garment Contract, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 69 -- Includes: contact sheets; Philadelphia audience; close-up of woman, New England Regional.
  - Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 70 -- Includes: meetings; officers and staff; Local 486 Waterville, ME meeting; Mike Cavanaugh, Evelyn Frazier.
  - Cotton Garment Negotiations - 1979. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 71 -- Includes: contact sheets; meetings.
  - Courtaulds. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 72 -- Includes: contract signing, Local 779T, Canada; Rolland Seguin, Leo Viau, Roy Collins, Harry Bough, Roger LaBonte, Jack Lindsay, Earl Ingram, Eugene Berniquer; Union and company officials: Dunton, Reyno
  - Couture, Jean-Marc., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 73 -- Includes: Couture speakers at 1979 Canadian Conference; Frazier, Clark, and Couture; Couture on plant floor; Canadian Joint Board executives attend a meeting with ACTWU's three top officers.
  - Cranston, Alan (Senator D-Cal)., 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 74 -- Includes: 1977 portrait; close- up; 1980 portrait.
  - Credit Card. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 75 -- Includes: Credit Card Presentation, NY Bank.
  - "Cry Freedom" - film. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 76 -- Includes: Universal Pictures movie shots, Denzel Washington.
  - Cuccio, Frank. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 77 -- Includes: Cuccio in chair.
  - Culver, John (D-Iowa). (Box 18, Folder 26)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 78 -- Includes: scenes in cornfield; close-up.
  - Cuomo, Mario., 1986 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 79 -- Includes: portrait; accepting ACTWU endorsement; Sheinkman, Jerry Landman, Cuomo; Cuomo speaking; close-up; City of Hope Dinner 12/13/86 contact sheets; Cuomo hugging man.
  - Cutters Class. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 80 -- Includes: man working.
  - Cutters' School Story Dec. 1988. (Box 18, Folder 29)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 81 -- Includes: slides; men working; contact sheets; demonstration of cutting.
  - Dabney, Henrietta., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 82 -- Includes: GEB 1977, woman at desk.
  - Daddario, Emilio Q. - Conn. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 83 -- Includes: close-up of man.
  - Dameron, Emma., 1981 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 84 -- Includes: close-ups; meetings; smoking cigarettes; at Convention 1981.
  - D'Amours, Norm Rep (D-NH). (Box 18, Folder 33)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 85 -- Includes: talking with worker in shop; giving speech; portrait; with microphone.
  - Dancers/Dance Groups. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 86 -- Includes: Amman Folk Dance Group performs, Los Angeles: San Francisco Ballet, Diana Weber and Jim Sohm as "Romeo and Juliet"; Martha Graham portrait; Suzanne Farrell portrait; "The Four Temperaments", M
  - Dantin, Maurice. (Box 18, Folder 35)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 87 -- Includes: speech shots.
  - Daughtry, Mabel. (Box 18, Folder 36)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 88 -- Includes: contact sheets; woman with dog.
  - Davidson, Monty., 1955-1980 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 89 -- Includes: portrait; street canvassing in Ontario (Cambridge) late 70's; at first constituency office in Cambridge, 1976; addressing Canadian conference ACTWU,1980; Davidson and Odoaro DiSanto; working a
  - Deaf Conference, NYC., 1991 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 90 -- Includes: contact sheets.
  - Debs, Eugene V. (Awards)., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 91 -- Includes: woman at table; photo of Debs; pamphlet from 1982 dinner.
  - Deep South Conference, Atlanta, GA., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 92 -- Includes: Mel Tate speech; August 1982 conference.
  - Deep South Region (Textile Div.)., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 93 -- Includes: August 1982 conference; Atlanta, officer installation; Jack Sheinkman; Walt Rainey; Gerald Brown; Clyde Bush; R.L Roper; Bruce Raynor.
  - Deep South Regional Jt. Bd. Meeting (Atlanta, GA). (Box 18, Folder 42)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 94 -- Includes: Tom Williams addresses delegates; Gerald Brown, Joe Gaines (Local 2280), Bruce Raynor, Clyde Bush, R.L Roper, Grady Collum (Local 1948-3).
  - DeFazio, Mauro. (Box 18, Folder 43)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 95 -- Includes: DeFazio honored at dinner: DeFazio with Sheinkman, DeFazio with Stetin; DeFazio in meeting.
  - Delaware Valley Joint Board (Textile Division). (Box 18, Folder 44)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 96 -- Includes: offices installation: Stephen Kopach, Russell Galante, Paul DeNardo, Dorothy Fox, Harry Fox.
  - Democratic National Convention ACTWU delegates., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 97 -- Includes: Demetrice Mondy, Local 1757-T; Jimmy Boone, Roanoke Valley Jt. Bd.; Jan Schakowsky, Local 2458; Patricia Mctlaffey, Local 931; Vivian Peck, Local 465-C retiree; Velma Clayton.
  - Democratic Convention, San Francisco, CA, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 98 -- Includes: Diana McCoy, Oregon delegate; Bennett Taylor and North Carolina delegation; Barbara Johnson and Sen. Paul Sarbanes, delegates from Maryland; Joyce Miller speaking at convention; Joan Suarez, d
  - Democratic Convention, 1976-1980 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 99 -- Includes: Mary Ward and Paul Restivo; Democratic Convention 1976; Democratic Convention NYC 1980; ACTWU delegates Democratic National Conference, NYC1976; breakfast for ACTWU delegates to Democratic Nat
  - Dent, John. (Box 18, Folder 48)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 100 -- Includes: close-up.
  - Denton Mills - Fulton, Miss. (Box 18, Folder 49)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 101 -- Includes: negotiating committee from Denton Mills Plants: Martha Jarrell, Danny Forsyth, Lucille Brewer, Jane Johnson, Culaw Manasco.
  - Dernomcourt, Wayne. (Box 18, Folder 50)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 2, ff 102 -- Includes: portrait; memo re: death; short bio; obituary; giving speech.
  - Detroit., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Includes: Audience at leadership school, Feb.1984 Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, also Includes group shots of retired members Christmas party.
  - Detroit Joint Board. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Includes: Group shots in shop and Group shots outside with city backdrop.
  - Diaz, Olga., 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Includes: ACTOR demonstration, Albany; Diaz and Cecil Toppin in Dominica; Diaz receiving NY Consumer Assembly's 1983 merit award from Jack Sheinkman and Joyce D. Miller; Diaz in Mexico with Maximino Molina, June 17, 1981; Diaz with Brian Carrol and Sydney
  - Diesel Cars. Volkswagen Rabbit, rear of. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dillman, George. Portraits. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dillon, James A. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Includes: portrait and biography of.
  - Dinkin, Bernie., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Includes: Portrait of Dinkin at podium of Philadelphia Legislative Conf. 4/75
  - Dinkins, David., 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Includes: ACTWU leafleting, 14th St. area 9/84; Susan Pinette, political action 1988; Dinkins shaking hands, wearing ACTWU hat; Dinkins Rally NY 11/89; Dinkins Rally 8/89; Labour Day 9/4/89; Speaking in front of union banner; Dinkins with Ruth Messinger O
  - Dinkins, David., 1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Includes: Dinkins at podium at rally wearing ACTWU hat; at Rally 6/89; with negs.
  - Dinos Menswear (cover 11/12/92).., 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Includes: Group shots on shop floor, including some with Clinton-Gore placard.
  - Dior Demo 10/92., 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Includes: Picketers in hallway
  - Di Paolo, Anthony., 1971-1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Includes: Testimonial, April 1971 and Obituary 12/76
  - Disability., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Includes: Disability Conference, S. California; Disability Research Project; Jose Menendez; Disability Research Project visiting shop 5/77.
  - Disability Project., 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Includes: Shop Chairman Sam Rizzo and Vincent Russo, Pres. of Local 278; David Coope- Disability Project, Labor Bookshelf, Allentown PA R& F Boycott Committee July 80; ACTWU members receiving heat treatments, Disability Project 4/78; Woman, with spinal
  - Disability Project Story (4/78)., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Includes: Shop Chairman Sam Rizzo with Steve Toth, Pres. of So. Cal. Joint Board and Local 639; Rizzo also on shop floor with workers; Disability Project Surveys, Members' Health Problems; Meeting, Project 4/78
  - DiSanto, Odoaro. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Includes: Posing in front of statue of John Sandfield MacDonald, PM of Ontario- 1867-1871.
  - District 65.:, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Includes: Sheinkman speaking at District 65 June 1974; District 65 Convention, Speeches 11/76 ACTWU.
  - District 1199., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Includes: Union musical "Take Care" 4/80.
  - Dixon, Alan. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Includes: Alan Dixon, Democratic Senator from Ill, at party, 86.
  - Dodd, Chris (D-Conn)., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Includes: Greeting Black woman at sewing machine, Portrait 10/80.
  - Doerr Electric Chicago, Ill (Local 1771)., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Includes: M(?)g. Comm.12/82.
  - Dole, Elizabeth. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Includes: Portrait of Secretary of Labor Elizabeth Dole.
  - Dominion Cord and Tassle (Canada)., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Includes: Negotiating Committee of DC and T, Bernice Perreault, Diane Lachapelle and Diane Dancause 11/79.
  - Donahue, Ed. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Includes: James O'Grady, Bert Seidman- AFL-CIO and speaking, Ed Donahue Pres. E.A.I. (?)
  - Donahue, Thomas R., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Includes: Donahue speaking at conference; Portrait of Donahue; Pres. Finley confers with new AFL-CIO Sec. Treas. Donahue, 12/79.
  - Donovan, Raymond J. (Box 3, Folder 26)